<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0354]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[MASTERTOOL pliers 22-0180]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Pliers 180 mm American type MASTERTOOL 22-0180. Designed for locksmith, assembly and other works. Made of high carbon steel, chrome plated. ]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Designed for locksmith, assembly and other works.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[230]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/4/22-0180.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0355]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Combination pliers 180 mm MASTERTOOL 23-0180]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Combination pliers 180 mm MASTERTOOL 23-0180. Designed for locksmith, assembly and other works. Made of carbon steel, partially oxidized. They are heat-treated with high strength characteristics working surfaces and hardened cutting edges. Equipped with comfortable plastic handles. ]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Designed for locksmith, assembly and other works. Made of carbon steel, partially oxidized. They are heat-treated with high strength characteristics working surfaces and hardened cutting edges.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[245]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/2/23-0180.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0356]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Multi-tool knife 9 in 1 + bits (case) SIGMA 4375511]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Multi-tool knife 9 in 1 + bits (case) SIGMA 4375511 is made on the basis of a full-fledged knife and is made of high quality stainless steel 3Cr13, contains a minimum set of necessary tools. The knife lies comfortably in the hand, thanks to the ergonomic shape of the handle. The knife has a partial serrated sharpening, which increases the efficiency of cutting laminated and fibrous materials, for example, nets, ropes, cables, and also increases the shelf life of the blade.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[ The knife has a partial serrated sharpening, which increases the efficiency of cutting laminated and fibrous materials, for example, nets, ropes, cables, and also increases the shelf life of the blade.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[345]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/138/4375511.jpeg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0357]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Multitool (12 in 1) STANLEY STHT0-28111]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Multi-tool (12 in 1) STANLEY STHT0-28111 has an anti-corrosion golden coating, which gives a beautiful visible appearance, as well as practicality and durable use. The handles of the tool are spring-loaded, which ensures comfortable work. The design is as strong as possible. The selection of tools allows you to perform a lot of work both during trips to nature and at home. All tools are easy to handle and can be easily removed from the overall structure. The folded length of the multitool is 100 mm, which allows it to be carried even in a pocket.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[The folded length of the multitool is 100 mm, which allows it to be carried even in a pocket.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[400]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/111/STHT0-28111.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0358]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Folding knife, handle with wooden inserts INTERTOOL HT-0594]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Designed for everyday chores, it will be useful on a hike or just in nature. It can become an indispensable attribute of your safety in difficult life situations. Put a knife in your pocket or bag and it will definitely help out!]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Folding knife, handle with wooden inserts INTERTOOL HT-0594 It is distinguished by its structural integrity, the shape of the knife can withstand heavy loads, and hardened steel 313 will not allow rusting. Sharpening stays sharp for a long time! ]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[231]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/115/intertool-ht-0594-source.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0359]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Folding knife INTERTOOL HT-0595]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[The lock is reliable and safe, protects the operator from accidental closing, while the knife can be folded easily and effortlessly by sliding the locking part to the side. There are special symmetrical pins on the blade of the knife, it is convenient to open the knife, both left-handed and right-handed.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Folding knife INTERTOOL HT-0595 The folding knife is distinguished by its light weight, while being sharp as a razor! ]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[272]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/115/intertool-ht-0595-source.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0360]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Multi-tool 12 in 1 with case INTERTOOL HT-0541]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Multi-tool 12 in 1 with cover INTERTOOL HT-0541 Will be a good helper in everyday life and in the car. An excellent gift for a motorist, fisherman, summer resident, cyclist and tourist. Due to the hardened alloy steel, the working edges are not erased, they are resistant to rust. All tools are rigidly fixed and do not give backlash in work. The body is made of anodized aluminum, lightweight and ergonomic, fits comfortably in the hand and does not cause discomfort when gripped strongly. The handles are hollow and lightweight, and the tools don't go overboard. Opening the desired nozzle comfortably and effortlessly will help the serifs on each of them.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[With this multitool, you take care of yourself, protecting yourself from unforeseen situations and daily hassles! ]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[245]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/115/intertool-ht-0541-source.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0361]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Cycling multi-tool 90 mm 16 in 1 + SIGMA accessories 4375621]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[A successful combination of versatility with functionality - a simple and reliable, multifunctional set consisting of tools that are often used during repair work. High-precision machining of the edges ensures precise fit of the tool in the splines (tenacity).]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Folds easily and fits in a bag or case. It will become an excellent companion not only for cycling enthusiasts, but also an irreplaceable tool in your car or in your home.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[214]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/152/4375621.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0362]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Folding knife 112 mm SIGMA 4375721]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Folding knife 112 mm (handle composite G10) SIGMA 4375721 - designed for constant wearing and operation. Like any knife, first of all, they are the simplest tool that allows you to solve a fairly large range of tasks. The model successfully combines both advanced and time-tested design solutions - a successful combination of a full-fledged knife and a set of tools consisting of a variety of bits, a screwdriver and an allen wrench.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[The knife has such dimensions and characteristics of the blade, butt and retainer, which are acceptable for free wearing and use. It is not included in the group of edged weapons to which legal restrictions on use apply.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[603]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/152/4375721.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0363]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Folding knife 165 mm, handle with wooden inserts INTERTOOL HT-0590]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Folding knife 165 mm, handle with wooden inserts INTERTOOL HT-0590]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Folding knife 165 mm, handle with wooden inserts INTERTOOL HT-0590]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[256]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/114/intertool-ht-0590-source.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0364]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Roof hammer, fiberglass handle]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Roof hammer 600 g, fiberglass handle INTERTOOL HT-0230 is designed for roofing work. The striker is square in shape, the toe is in the shape of a nailer, in which one of the canines has been cut by 2/3, thanks to which it is possible to easily hook materials.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[The working part is made of high quality tool steel.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[187]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/2/intertool-ht-0230-source.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0365]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Tinsmith hammer 35 mm]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Has a metal handle. Equipped with replaceable plastic strikers equipped with a special threaded fastener for quick change, which allows you to choose the type of striker required for a particular operation.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Designed for work with materials that are sensitive to mechanical stress.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[125]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/4/02-0330.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0366]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Bayonet shovel "American" 250 х 210 mm 14-6220]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[A metal shovel designed for gardening, construction and earthwork.]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[A metal shovel designed for gardening, construction and earthwork.]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[144]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/4/14-6220.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0367]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Garden pruner stainless steel MASTERTOOL 14-6110]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Garden pruner stainless steel 215 mm  MASTERTOOL 14-6110]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Garden pruner stainless steel 215 mm  MASTERTOOL 14-6110]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[190]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/6/14-6110.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0368]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Universal hacksaw "3 in 1" STANLEY 0-20-092]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Such a canvas is not prone to getting stuck or bent during use. Design with rotary blade lock. It is convenient to store all three canvases, to choose the angle of installation of the curtain (6 positions).]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Blade for wood with a length of 250 mm 11 TPI cuts when moving "towards itself".]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[355]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/102/0-20-092.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
	<node>
		<sku><![CDATA[T0369]]></sku>
		<title><![CDATA[Shrub shears 550 mm MASTERTOOL 14-6130]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[Features and benefits of the model - carbon steel blade C55, TPR coated handles]]></description>
		<desc><![CDATA[Features and benefits of the model - carbon steel blade C55, TPR coated handles]]></desc>
		<price><![CDATA[171]]></price>
		<image><![CDATA[https://shoptool.com.ua/images/thumbnails/550/450/detailed/105/14-6130.jpg]]></image>
	</node>
</data>
